Guide to the Frank J. Donner Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Informers and Surveillance Files, 1897-1983; Series II
  - Individuals
    - Durham, Douglas, undated (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Eckhert, Kenneth, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Edmiston, Martha N. and John J., 1950, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Evans, Timothy, Jr., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - Fisher, Paul, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Foard, William, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Franz, Art
    - Gitlow, Benjamin
      - Clippings and pamphlets, 1948-1953, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 176)
      - Notes and testimony, 1939, 1951, undated (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Glass, Stanley, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Glatis, James W., 1954 (Box 11, Folder 179)
    - Goff, Kenneth, 1937, 1947-1948, undated (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Grathwohl, Larry
      - General, 1969-1973, undated (Box 11, Folder 181)
      - Clippings, 1970-1975, undated (Box 11, Folder 182)
      - Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 183)
      - Senate testimony, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 184 - 185)
      - Writings
    - Grimm, Charles R., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 186)
    - Haddock, Hoyt, 1936-1937, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 187)
    - Hall, Gordon, undated (Box 11, Folder 188)
    - Hamlin, Lloyd, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 189)
    - Hardy, Robert, 1972, undated (Box 12, Folder 190 - 193)
    - Harper, Clark, undated (Box 12, Folder 194)
    - Harris, Robert, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 195)
    - Harris, William H., 1953, undated (Box 12, Folder 196)
    - Hartle, Barbara, 1954, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 197)
    - Heisler, Edward
      See: Series III. Subject Files, 1941-1992 Folder 439 See: Series III. Subject Files, 1941-1992 Folder 440 - 449
    - Heltzinger, Robert, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 198)
    - Herron, Garfield, undated (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - Hess, Carl, undated (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - Hewitt, George (a.k.a. Tim Holmes)
      - Clippings, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 201)
      - Correspondence, 1940-1948 (Box 12, Folder 202)
      - Testimony and notes, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 203)
    - Hidalgo, Balmes, 1952, undated (Box 12, Folder 204)
    - Holmes, William Clifford, 1949, undated (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - Honig, Nathaniel
      - Clippings, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 206)
      - Communist Party of the United States of America publications [edited by Honig], 1932-1934 (Box 12, Folder 207)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1956, undated (Box 12, Folder 208)
      - Legal documents, 1941-1955, undated (Box 12, Folder 209)
      - Testimonies
        - Abstracts and indexes, 1948, undated (Box 13, Folder 210)
        - Bridges, Harry
          - Deportation hearing, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 211)
          - United States v. Bridges, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 212)
        - Deportation hearings, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 213)
        - International Woodworkers' trial, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 214)
        - United States v. Eulogio de la Cruz, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 215)
    - Hook, Sidney, 1946-1949, undated (Box 13, Folder 216)
    - Huber, John J., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 217)
    - Janowitz, John, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 218)
    - Johnson, Manning
      - Clippings, 1954-1958 (Box 13, Folder 219)
      - Notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 220)
      - Testimonies
        - Abstracts and excerpts, 1948-1956 (Box 13, Folder 221 - 223)
        - Bohlinger v. International Worker's Order, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 224)
        - House Committee on Un-American Activities, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 225)
        - Immigration and Naturalization Service [re: Nat Yanish], 1948 (Box 14, Folder 226 - 228)
      - Writings, 1935-1935, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 229)
    - Kawano, Jack, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 230)
    - Keller, James, undated (Box 14, Folder 231)
    - King, Jay (a.k.a. "Tommy the Terrible")
      - Clippings, 1970, undated (Box 14, Folder 232)
      - Interviews, 1971, undated (Box 14, Folder 233 - 234)
    - Kirk, Gerald
      - Congressional testimony, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 235 - 236)
      - Notes, interviews, and clippings, 1970, undated (Box 14, Folder 237)
    - Koehler, William Joseph
      See: Series III. Subject Files, 1941-1992 Folder 469
    - Kornfeder, Joseph Zack
      - Biographical information, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 238)
      - Clippings, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 239)
      - Correspondence, 1936, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 240)
      - Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 241)
      - Testimonies
        - Abstracts and indexes, 1949-1957 (Box 15, Folder 242 - 243)
        - Miscellaneous, 1948-1951, undated (Box 15, Folder 244 - 250)
      - Union materials, 1936-1937, 1957, undated (Box 15, Folder 251)
      - Writings, 1927-1939 (Box 15, Folder 252)
    - Kravchenko, Victor A., 1947 (Box 15, Folder 253)
    - Lautner, John
      - Biographical information, undated (Box 15, Folder 254 - 255)
      - Clippings, 1952, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 256)
      - Correspondence
        - Donner, Frank, 1953-1961 (Box 16, Folder 257)
        - Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 258)
      - Notes, 1949, 1952, undated (Box 16, Folder 259)
      - Testimonies
        - Abstracts and indexes, 1952-1955, undated (Box 16, Folder 260)
        - Cross examination, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 261)
        - Expertise on Marxist-Leninism, undated (Box 16, Folder 262)
        - Miscellaneous, 1954, undated (Box 16, Folder 263)
      - Writings, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 264)
      - Miscellaneous documents, 1952, 1955, undated (Box 16, Folder 265)
    - Lawlor, Vince Ann, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 266)
    - Leech, John
      - Biographical information, 1949, undated (Box 16, Folder 267)
      - Testimony, 1950, undated (Box 16, Folder 268)
    - Lemmer, William
    - Long, Ralph V., 1939-1955 (Box 16, Folder 269)
    - Mackie, Barbara, undated (Box 16, Folder 270)
    - Malkin, Maurice
      - Biographical information, undated (Box 16, Folder 271)
      - Correspondence, 1939, 1950-1951, undated (Box 16, Folder 272)
      - Legal documents, 1949-1956 (Box 16, Folder 273)
      - Notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 274)
    - Mandel, Benjamin, [1948] (Box 16, Folder 275)
    - Markheim, Irving, 1955, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 276)
    - Markward, Mary Stalcup
      - Legal documents and clippings, 1952-1953, undated (Box 16, Folder 277)
      - Testimony before the House Committee on Un-American Activities, 1951, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 278 - 279)
    - Martinez, Frank, undated (Box 17, Folder 280)
    - Matthews, Joseph B., 1948, undated (Box 17, Folder 281)
    - Matusow, Harvey
      - Clippings
        - General, 1950-1957 (Box 17, Folder 282 - 284)
        - Left wing press, 1951-1958 (Box 17, Folder 285)
      - Confession, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 286)
      - Handwriting analysis, 1952, undated (Box 17, Folder 287)
      - Notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 288)
      - Testimonies
        - Abstracts, 1952, 1954, undated (Box 17, Folder 289)
        - United States v. Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, 1952, 1955, undated (Box 17, Folder 290)
        - Harrison, Will, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 291)
        - Jacobs, Ruth, 1952, undated (Box 17, Folder 292)
        - United States v. Clinton Jencks, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 293)
    - Mazzei, Joseph
      - Clippings, 1954-1967 (Box 17, Folder 294)
      - Correspondence [to Frank Donner], 1956 (Box 17, Folder 295)
      - Labor documents and pamphlets, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 296)
      - Legal documents, 1954-1955, undated (Box 17, Folder 297 - 298)
      - Testimonies
        - Indexes, 1954-1955, undated (Box 17, Folder 299)
        - House Committee on Un-American Activities [with Mary Mazzei], 1954, undated (Box 17, Folder 300)
    - McCracken, Wayne, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 301)
    - McIntyre, Bruce, undated (Box 18, Folder 302)
    - Meinshausen, Don
      - Interview, undated (Box 18, Folder 303 - 304)
      - Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 305)
    - Meyer, Frank S., 1951, 1953, undated (Box 18, Folder 306)
    - Mikkelsen, Harold, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 307)
    - Miller, Max (a.k.a George Ellison), undated (Box 18, Folder 308)
    - Mosher, Harold, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 309)
    - Mosher, Thomas
      - Biographical information, undated (Box 18, Folder 310)
      - Clippings, 1968-1972 (Box 18, Folder 311)
      - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 312)
      - Notes and photograph, undated (Box 18, Folder 313)
      - Testimony, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 314)
      - Writings re: Mosher ["The Terrorist" by Steve Weissman and Herb Borock], 1975 (Box 18, Folder 315)
    - Natvig, Marie, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 316)
    - Neal, John
      - General, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 317)
      - Clippings, 1974-1978 (Box 18, Folder 318)
    - Nee, John Francis, undated (Box 18, Folder 319)
    - Nestler, Frank, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 320)
    - Nicodemus, Charles, 1947-1954 (Box 18, Folder 321)
    - Ondrejka, Michael, undated (Box 18, Folder 322)
    - Owens, Harry Bartlett, 1952, undated (Box 18, Folder 323)
    - Pace, John, 1951, undated (Box 18, Folder 324)
    - Parker, Horse, 1970s (Box 18, Folder 325)
    - Patterson, Leonard
      - Biographical information, 1949-1953, undated (Box 18, Folder 326)
      - Deposition transcript, undated (Box 18, Folder 327)
    - Pell, Mike, 1952, undated (Box 18, Folder 328)
    - Philbrick, Herbert A.
      - Clippings, 1952-1971 (Box 18, Folder 329)
      - Communist Party of the United States of America, 1952-1957 (Box 18, Folder 330)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1957, undated (Box 18, Folder 331)
      - Flyers and publicity, 1944-1962, undated (Box 18, Folder 332)
      - Testimonies
        - Abstracts, 1951-1956 (Box 18, Folder 333)
        - House Committee on Un-American Activities, undated (Box 18, Folder 334)
      - Writings by Philbrick, 1939, 1951-1956, undated (Box 18, Folder 335 - 336)
    - Poe, Emerson Leroy
      See: Series III. Subject Files, 1941-1992 Folder 487
    - Powers, George
      - Biographical information, 1939, 1951-1956 undated (Box 19, Folder 337)
      - Correspondence and personal statements, 1937, undated (Box 19, Folder 338)
      - International Workers Order, 1929-1939 (Box 19, Folder 339)
    - Rosen, Jacob, 1963-1965 (Box 19, Folder 340)
    - Rosser, Lou, 1928, 1946, 1952, undated (Box 19, Folder 341)
    - Rowe, Gary Thomas, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 342)
    - Russell, Louis J., 1948 (Box 19, Folder 343)
    - Sage, E. J. Parker, 1948, undated (Box 19, Folder 344)
    - Salisbury, Wayne, undated (Box 19, Folder 345)
    - Sannes, David
      - Interviews, 1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 346 - 347)
      - Legal documents, 1968, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 348)
      - Statements, 1968, 1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 349)
    - Santwire, Milton J., 1953 (Box 19, Folder 350)
    - Saunders, David, 1952, undated (Box 19, Folder 351)
    - Scarletto, Daniel, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 352)
    - Schafer, Harry E. and Jill, 1970, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 353)
    - Schemanske, Stephen J., 1953 (Box 19, Folder 354)
    - Scott, Cecil
      - Biographical information, 1947-1953 (Box 19, Folder 355)
      - Clippings, 1952-1955 (Box 19, Folder 356)
      - Legal and mental health documents, 1924, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 357)
      - Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 358)
      - Organizing reports for United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 359)
    - Siegel, Sheldon
      See: Series III. Subject Files, 1941-1992 Folder 240 - 251
    - Silvers, Max, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 360)
    - Strunk, Arthur Paul, undated (Box 19, Folder 361)
    - Sumaya, Fernando, undated (Box 19, Folder 362)
    - Tatman, Robert F., 1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 363)
    - Teto, William H., 1953, 1955, undated (Box 19, Folder 364)
    - Thomas, Herman E., 1954 (Box 19, Folder 365)
    - Tongyai, Thomas [a.k.a. "Tommy the Traveler"]
      - Clippings (general), 1970-1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 366)
      - Correspondence, 1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 367)
      - Hobart College
        - Clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 368)
        - Legal Defense Fund, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 369)
        - President's Commission on Campus Unrest: Investigation of Hobart College, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 370)
      - Interviews, undated (Box 19, Folder 371)
      - Notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 372 - 373)
    - Vale, Rena, undated (Box 20, Folder 374)
    - Weatherford, Jack
      - Interviews, undated (Box 20, Folder 375)
      - Notes and clippings, 1970-1974 (Box 20, Folder 376)
    - Weber, Simon, 1935-1940 (Box 20, Folder 377)
    - Weiner, Steve, undated (Box 20, Folder 378)
    - Wereb, Stephen, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 379)
    - White, Charles D., 1935, 1950, 1952, undated (Box 20, Folder 380)
    - Yergan, Max, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 381)
    - Younglove, Thomas, 1952, undated (Box 20, Folder 382)
    - Zygmont, Thaddeus, 1897, 1904, 1934-1935, undated (Box 20, Folder 383)
    - Note card indexes on informers
      - B-J, undated (Box 21)
      - K-W, undated (Box 22)
      - B-W [separate alphabetical run], undated (Box 23)
  - Localities
    - Duke University, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 384 - 385)
    - Harvard University, undated (Box 24, Folder 386)
    - Kent State University
      - General, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 387)
      - Clippings, 1970-1972, undated (Box 24, Folder 388)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1972, undated (Box 24, Folder 389)
    - New Orleans
      - Black Panther Party, 1970, undated (Box 24, Folder 390)
      - State of Louisiana, Joint Legislative Committee on Un-American Activities, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 391)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 392)
    - Seattle [includes material from Coalition on Government Spying], 1977-1978, undated (Box 24, Folder 393 - 395)
    - Stanford University/Palo Alto, California
      - Clippings, 1966-1971 (Box 24, Folder 396 - 397)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 398)
      - Interview, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 399)
      - Legal documents, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 400 - 402)
      - Note cards, undated (Box 25, Folder 403)
      - Writings, undated (Box 25, Folder 404)
    - State University of New York, Brockport, 1967, undated (Box 25, Folder 405 - 406)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 407)
    - University of Florida, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 408)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, correspondence, and notes regarding surveillance on university campuses, 1962-1973, undated (Box 25, Folder 409 - 412)
  - Non-political informers, 1926, 1963-1978, undated (Box 25, Folder 413 - 415)
- Subject Files, 1941-1992; Series III
  Arranged alphabetically by individual and corporate names and topical headings, the series consists of a large variety of materials relating to a broad set of subjects that represent Donner's research interests and political and legal activities. Most of the files were collected, rather than created, by Donner. The files include correspondence, publications, legal documents, clippings, audio tapes, ephemera, and other materials relating to political organizations and movements, court cases, and government agencies and programs. Many of the files complement information found in other series, particularly the Individuals files of Series II. While cross-references have been made where feasible, they are not comprehensive.
  Extensive files document many social and political protest groups and movements from the 1960s, 1970s, and 1980s, particularly those which faced legal charges based on the testimony of informers. The groups from the 1960s and 1970s include the American Indian Movement, the Camden Twenty-Eight, the Harrisburg Seven, the Seattle Liberation Front, and Vietnam Veterans Against the War. Groups from the 1980s include the Jewish Defense League, as well as a host of organizations that sympathized with leftist revolutionary movements in Latin America, including Committee In Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), the Movement Support Network, and a range of religious and political groups that are filed under the broad heading of the "Sanctuary movement." A particularly rich set of files document surveillance and informer activities in the Chicago area. They are dispersed throughout the following files: Alliance to End Repression, Chicago Peace Council, Chicago Police Department, Chicago Political Surveillance Litigation and Education Project, Socialist Workers Party, and a portion of the American Civil Liberties Union files. There is also documentation on other political and social protest organizations including the American Civil Liberties Union, the American Friends Service Committee, Campaign for Political Rights, the Christic Institute, and the Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA). Donner also accumulated a set of files that document the protest movement against nuclear arms. Following Donner's own arrangement scheme, files of several anti-nuclear groups are listed collectively under the heading "Nuclear Freeze Movement."
  Most likely in support of his unpublished book on government malfeasance during the 1980s, "Exploring the Wreckage" (see Series IV), Donner also compiled multiple files relating to mainstream political issues and scandals of the 1980s. Notable topics include abortion (found under National Abortion Federation and Planned Parenthood), pornography (found under Attorney General's Commission on Pornography), legal aid (found under Legal Services Corporation), and the Iran/Contra scandal. Donner also put together files on several individuals nominated for federal judgeships and other government positions in the 1980s, including Robert Bork, Herbert Ellingswood, Anthony Kennedy, David Manion, Antonin Scalia, and David Treen.
  Files relating to individual court cases and deportation hearings comprise another significant portion of the series. The cases are filed under the names of the primary individuals involved. Donner served as counsel for some of these cases and as an advisor for others.
  - Accuracy in Media, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Advance, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Alan Gutmacher Institute, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Alliance for Justice
    - "Contempt for Law: Excluding the Public from the Rulemaking Process" [report], 1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Judicial Selection Project, 1988, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Alliance to End Repression
    - General, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Cassel, Doug, 1978, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Notes, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee
    - General, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Court documents [American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee, et al. v. Edwin Meese III, et al.], 1987 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - American Civil Liberties Union
    - Affirmative action [Grove City College decision], 1986 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Civil Liberties Alert, 1977-1991 (Box 26, Folder 12 - 13)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1989, undated (Box 26, Folder 14 - 15)
    - Court documents [ACLU v. City of Chicago], 1977 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - FBI charter legislation [ACLU statement], 1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Free Trade in Ideas Conference, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Nuclear freeze activities
      See: Series III. Subject Files, 1941-1992 Folder 329
    - The Privacy Report, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Reports, 1984-1991, undated (Box 27, Folder 20 - 21)
    - Reproductive Freedom Project, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966, 1977, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - American Federation of Labor/Congress of Industrial Organizations [Union Lawyers Conference], 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - American Friends Service Committee
    - General, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 25 - 26)
    - Nuclear Freeze activities
    - Program on Government Surveillance and Citizen's Rights, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - American Indian Movement
    - Clippings, 1974-1977, undated (Box 27, Folder 28 - 30)
    - Durham, Douglas [informer]
      See: Series II. Informers and Surveillance Files, 1897-1983 Folder 170
    - Legal documents
      - United States v. Leonard Crowdog, Carter Camp, and Stanley Holder, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 31 - 35)
      - United States v. Mark Joseph Fleury, Reginald Karl Dodge, Larry A. Downs, and Colin Robin Wesaw and United States v. Manuel Alvarado and Terry Gene Williams, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 36 - 38)
      - Wounded Knee trial, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 39)
      - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - American Opinion, 1968, 1972, undated (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - American Peace Crusade, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Americans United for the Separation of Church and State, undated (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - America's Watch [re: United States training of foreign police], 1986 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Attorney General's Commission on Pornography ["Meese Commission"]
    - American Civil Liberties Union reports, 1985-1988, undated (Box 28, Folder 45 - 46)
    - Clippings, 1985-1988 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - National Coalition Against Censorship report, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Notes, undated (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Senate Judiciary Committee testimony, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Attorney General's Guidelines for FBI Foreign Intelligence Collection and Foreign Counterintelligence Investigations, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Biddle, Francis [nomination for attorney general], 1941 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Blichfeldt, Julius B. [deportation hearings], 1949 (Box 29, Folder 53 - 54)
  - Mitchell Bloch, et al. v. Edwin Meese, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Bork, Robert, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Bridges, Harry [deportation trial], 1941, 1945, undated (Box 29, Folder 57)
    See also: Box 7, Folder 98-99
    See also: Series II. Informers and Surveillance Files, 1897-1983 Folder 211
    See also: Series II. Informers and Surveillance Files, 1897-1983 Folder 212
  - Bullfrog Films, Inc.
    - General, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Bullfrog Films, Inc., et al. v. Charles Z. Wick, Director of United States Information Agency, et al., 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 59 - 60)
  - California Assembly Committee on Constitutional Amendments [hearings regarding limitations on the rights of Communists], 1962 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Camden Twenty-Eight
    - Clippings, 1970-1973, undated (Box 29, Folder 62 - 63)
    - Correspondence with David Kairys, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Court documents, [1971-1973] (Box 30, Folder 65 - 71)
    - Fact book interviews, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 72)
    - Hardy, Robert [informer]
      See: Series II. Informers and Surveillance Files, 1897-1983 Folder 190 - 193
    - Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Campaign for Political Rights
    - Correspondence [with Donner], 1982 (Box 30, Folder 74)
    - First Principles [newsletter], 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 75)
    - Publicity, 1982, undated (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - Campaign to End Intelligence Abuse, 1976, undated (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1982-1992, undated (Box 30, Folder 78 - 79)
  - Center for Investigative Reporting, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 80)
  - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1986-1992 (Box 31, Folder 81 - 82)
  - Center for National Security Studies
    - General, 1981, undated (Box 31, Folder 83)
    - [newsletter], 1976-1992 (Box 31, Folder 84 - 88)
    - Reports, 1976, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 89)
  - Central Intelligence Agency Information Act, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 90)
  - Charleston Gazette (West Virginia), 1976 (Box 31, Folder 91)
  - Chernin, Rose, 1948-1957 (Box 31, Folder 92)
  - Chicago Peace Council, undated (Box 31, Folder 93)
  - Chicago Police Department [spying activities], 1969-1977 (Box 31, Folder 94 - 95)
  - Chicago Political Surveillance Litigation and Education Project, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 96)
  - Chino Escape Case, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 97)
  - Christic Institute, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 98 - 99)
  - Committee for Public Justice, 1978-1989 (Box 32, Folder 100)
  - Committee In Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES) [includes material regarding Center for Constitutional Rights]
    - Clippings, 1981-1991, undated (Box 32, Folder 101 - 103)